Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files A-E, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files D
    - Dickerson, James (Box A-34, Folder 39)
      Photographer if identified: US Coast Guard Reserve
    - Dickerson, Granville (Box A-34, Folder 40)
      Also newspaper clipping.
    - Dickerson, Nathaniel (Box A-34, Folder 41)
    - Dickerson, Roger (Box A-34, Folder 42)
      Photographer if identified: Sidney A. Tabak, Channel 21, Long Island Educational Television Council Inc.
    - Dickerson, Ron (Box A-34, Folder 43)
    - Dickerson, Valerie (Box A-34, Folder 44)
    - Dickins, Inez (Box A-34, Folder 45)
    - Dickinson, Angie (Box A-34, Folder 46)
    - Dickinson, Arthur (Box A-34, Folder 47)
    - Dickman, Joseph L. (Box A-34, Folder 48)
      Photographer if identified: Official NORAD Photo
    - Dicks, Caletha (Box A-34, Folder 49)
    - Dickson, David W. D. (Box A-34, Folder 50)
    - Dickson, G. Donald (Box A-34, Folder 51)
    - Dickson, J. R. (Box A-34, Folder 52)
    - Dickson, James (Box A-34, Folder 53)
      1 print has typescript press release stapled to recto. One print has staple through edge.
    - Diddley, Bo (Box A-34, Folder 54)
    - DiFalco, Samuel S. (Judge) (See Nathan Smith) (Box A-34, Folder 55)
      Photographer if identified: C.A. Ramsey
    - Diggs, Bertha J. Mrs. (Box A-34, Folder 56)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Landess
    - Diggs, Charles (Box A-34, Folder 57)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo,
    - Diggs, Charles (Box A-34, Folder 58)
    - Diggs, Charles Jr. Mr & Mrs. (Box A-34, Folder 59)
      Also 4 velox prints. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, United Press International, Dennis Clark
    - Diggs, J. Daniel (Box A-34, Folder 60)
    - Diggs, Estelle Mrs. (Box A-34, Folder 61)
      Also 2 velox prints. 2 groups of 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, A. Hansen
    - Diggs, Estelle (Box A-34, Folder 62)
    - Diggs, Ivery (Box A-34, Folder 63)
    - Diggs, Larry (Box A-34, Folder 64)
    - Diggs, Lawrence (Box A-34, Folder 65)
    - Diggs, Marilyn (Box A-34, Folder 66)
    - Diggs, Mary Huff (Dr.) (Box A-34, Folder 67)
      Photographer if identified: The Girl Scout Council
    - Diggs, Renee (Box A-34, Folder 68)
      Photographer if identified: Gary Gershoff
    - Diggs, Wesley Father of wife and 4 slain children (Box A-34, Folder 69)
    - Diggs, William Dr. (Box A-34, Folder 70)
    - Dike, Kenneth Onwuka (Dr.) (Box A-34, Folder 71)
    - Dilday, Bill (Box A-34, Folder 72)
    - Dildy, Ingrid Mrs. (Box A-34, Folder 73)
    - DiLeonardo, Jackqueline (Box A-34, Folder 74)
    - Dill, Donna (Box A-34, Folder 75)
    - Dill, John R. Dr. (Box A-34, Folder 76)
    - Dillahunt, Jim (Box A-34, Folder 77)
      Photographer if identified: Thomasine Barton-Gangadean, Harris Photo
    - Dillard, Al (Box A-34, Folder 78)
      Photographer if identified: Standard Photo Service
    - Dillard, Audrey E. (Box A-34, Folder 79)
    - Dillard, Emma (Box A-34, Folder 80)
      Photographer if identified: The Bing Studio
    - Dillard, Mimi (Box A-34, Folder 81)
    - Dillard, Peggy (Box A-34, Folder 82)
    - Dillard, Zoe (Box A-34, Folder 83)
      Photographer if identified: Queens County Cancer Society
    - Dilligard, Calvin (Box A-34, Folder 84)
    - Dillow, Leo (Box A-34, Folder 85)
    - Dillon, Maria (Box A-34, Folder 86)
    - Dillrao, Harrison (Box A-34, Folder 87)
    - DiLucia, Gil (Box A-34, Folder 88)
    - Dilworth, Charles T. (Box A-34, Folder 89)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Harris Photo
    - Dilworth, Chris (Box A-34, Folder 90)
    - Dilworth-Leslie, Samuel (Box A-34, Folder 91)
    - DiMaggio, Joe (Box A-34, Folder 92)
    - Di Marie (Box A-34, Folder 93)
    - Dimensions Unlimited (Box A-34, Folder 94)
    - Dimples (Box A-34, Folder 95)
    - Dimitry, Ernest L. (Box A-34, Folder 96)
    - Duran, Roberto (Box A-34, Folder 97)
      Photographer if identified: Smooth Gary
    - Dine and Dance (Box A-34, Folder 98)
      Photographer if identified: Photo by Edge
    - Dingell, John O. (Box A-34, Folder 99)
      Pictured in photo: Rev. Floyd Flake, Harrison Goldin, and Bishop Frank Cummings.
    - Dingle, Clinton H. Miss (Box A-34, Folder 100)
    - Dingle, Hazel (Box A-34, Folder 101)
    - Dingle, Julius (Box A-34, Folder 102)
    - Dinns, Sam (Box A-34, Folder 103)
    - Dinizulu (Box A-34, Folder 104)
    - Dinizulu, Gus (Box A-34, Folder 105)
      Photographer if identified: Priscilla Taylor
    - Dinkins (Box A-34, Folder 106)
      2 prints have caption stapled to recto. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons, Morgan O. McGivern, Allen Morgan, Joe Pineiro, Joan Vitale Strong, Bill Moore, Philip J. Carvalho, Karl Crutchfield
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 107)
      5 prints have staples through edge. Also one halftone print.
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Joan Vitale Strong, Allen Morgan, Larry Brown
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 108)
      7 prints have staples through edge. 5 groups of 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Peterkin Photo, Karl Crutchfield, Joan Vitale Strong, David Karp, Nat Valentine, Hakim Mutlaq
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 109)
      14 prints have staples through edge. Also 2 halftone prints.
      Photographer if identified: Marbeth, Joan Vitale Strong, Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, City of New York Dept. of Sanitation
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 110)
      Also one halftone print. 9 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Joseph Sinnott, Bill Moore, Joan Vitale Strong, Peterkin Photo, Richard Cohen Associates
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 111)
      Note written on envelope "For David Dinkins see special file near front of library."
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, James Gilbert, Karl Crutchfield, Lia Chang, Allen Morgan, Hakim Mutlaq
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 112)
      4 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons, Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Hakim Mutlaq, Larry Fine, Allen Morgan, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Joan Vitale Strong, James Gilbert
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 113)
      Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan, Joan Vitale Strong, James Gilbert, Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 114)
      5 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Joan Vitale Strong, Peterkin Photo, Elaine Velaochaga, Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Peter Pouchon
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 115)
      2 prints attached by staple. 6 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Curt Clemons, Peterkin Photo, Joan Vitale Strong, Karl Crutchfield, Allen Morgan, Bruce Williams, Lloyd Yearwood, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Ronald Glassman
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 116)
      6 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Kathryn Kirk, Kenneth S. Siegel, Joan Vitale Strong, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Joe Vericker, Curt Clemons
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-34, Folder 117)
      2 prints attached by staple.
      Photographer if identified: Joan Vitale Strong, Leonard Boykin, Peterkin Photo, Curt Clemons, Bill Moore
    - Dinkins, David (Atty. Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-34, Folder 118)
      2 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints attached by staple. 2 prints attached by tape. 2 prints have a newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Miriam Fishman, Shelley Brown, Curt Clemons, Pictorial Enterprise, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Allen Morgan, Chris Griffith
    - Dinkins, David (Atty. Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-34, Folder 119)
      1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso. 2 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Newell Johnson, Al Burley, Governor Morris Studios, Curt Clemons, Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Manhattan Community College, Ralph Cooper, David McAdams, James Gilbert, Cecil Layne, Alix, DeJean, Bruce Williams, Bill Moore, Rob Schoenbaum, Larry Brown,
    - Dinkins, David (Atty. Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-34, Folder 120)
      One print has staple through edge. 2 groups of prints are stuck together, one has approximately 5 and the other has approximately 4. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Al Burley, George Frye,
    - Dinkins, David (Atty. Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-34, Folder 121)
      Also 2 velox prints. 2 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Negro Press Photo Service, Hairston Photo, Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Dave Greene, Curt Clemons, David LeShay, Eugene Grossman
    - Dinkins, David (Atty. Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-34, Folder 122)
      14 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints are stuck together with paste. 2 prints have typescript caption stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Joe Thompson, Standard Studios, Allen Morgan, Marlis Momber, Peterkin Photo, James Gilbert, Harris Photo, Bert Andrews, Jerry Soalt, Bill Burlingham
    - Mayor Elect David Dinkins (Box A-34, Folder 123)
      11 prints have staples through edge. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan, Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Curt Clemons, Wali Amin Muhammad, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield
    - Mayor Elect David Dinkins (Box A-34, Folder 124)
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Pictorial Enterprise, Steve Berman,
    - Mayor Elect David Dinkins (Box A-34, Folder 125)
      Photographer if identified: David A. Zickl. Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Hakim Mutlaq, Delroy Davis, Leslie Kaliades, Joan Vitale Strong, Malcolm Pinckney, Pictorial Enterprise, Peterkin Photo,
    - Mayor Elect David Dinkins (Box A-34, Folder 126)
      2 prints have staples through edge. Program for 9-29-1989 Clergy Breakfast.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Peterkin Photo, Chris Griffith, Edward Reed, Pictorial Enterprise, Bruce Williams
    - Mayor Dinkins (Box A-34, Folder 127)
      One print has staple through edge. 1 print has newspaper clipping attached to verso. 2 prints are taped to photocopied article. Also 11-8-1993 report from NNPA, voting both ballot from 11-2-1993 election, photocopied article about Dinkins and art, 4 long press releases from August 1993, several newspaper clippings, 11 faxes from Mayor's office, one program from Eleanor Roosevelt Medallion awards program 11-22-1993, 2 copies of press release from Columbia University, and one newspaper ad from United Block Front Street Association.
      Photographer if identified: Joan Vitale Strong, Bill Moore, Allen Morgan
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-35, Folder 1)
      Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Bruce Williams, Dave Greene, Eugene Grossman
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-35, Folder 2)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Isaac Berez, Camera 1, Harris Photo, Ralph Cooper, Robert Espier, Bill Moore, Lem Peterkin, Curt Clemons
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-35, Folder 3)
      Photographer if identified: Juanita M. Cole, Curt Clemons, Monroe S. Frederick II, Bill Moore, Allen Morgan, Pictorial Enterprise, Robert Espier
    - Dinkins, David (Box A-35, Folder 4)
      Photographer if identified: Miriam Fishman, Allen Morgan, Pictorial Enterprise, Curt Coleman, Peterkin Photo, Copper Cunningham
    - Dinkins, David (Veloxes) (Box A-35, Folder 5)
      Photographer if identified: Joan Vitale Strong, Allen Morgan, Chris Griffith, Karl Crutchfield
    - Dinkins, David (Box OS-1, Folder 1)
      Portrait and photo in part of a larger collage.
    - Dinkins, David, Jr. (Box A-35, Folder 6)
    - Dinkins, Edith (Mrs.) (Box A-35, Folder 7)
    - Dinkins, Joyce (Box A-35, Folder 8)
    - Dinkins, Joyce (Box A-35, Folder 9)
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Joan Vitale Strong, Bill Moore, Allen Morgan
    - Dion, Little (Box A-35, Folder 10)
    - Diop, Al (Box A-35, Folder 11)
    - Diop, Alioune (Box A-35, Folder 12)
    - Diop, Suzanne (Box A-35, Folder 13)
    - Diolotelli (Ambassador) (Box A-35, Folder 14)
    - Diouf, Abdon (President of Senegal) (Box A-35, Folder 15)
      Photographer if identified: Jo Fielder
    - Diplomats, The (Box A-35, Folder 16)
    - Dire, Karen (Box A-35, Folder 17)
    - Director, Walter (Box A-35, Folder 18)
    - Dirkson, Everett (Box A-35, Folder 19)
      Photographer if identified: United Press International, The Boys Club of New York
    - Disco (Box A-35, Folder 20)
    - Discrimination (Box A-35, Folder 21)
    - Dash, Charlene (Box A-35, Folder 22)
      One velox print. Folder mislabeled "Dish, Charlene."
    - DiSilia, Frank (Box A-35, Folder 23)
    - Dismond, Samuel (Dr.) (Box A-35, Folder 24)
    - Dismuke, Claude (Box A-35, Folder 25)
    - Disney (Box A-35, Folder 26)
    - Disney Inn, The/Walt Disney World (Box A-35, Folder 27)
    - Disney on Parade (Box A-35, Folder 28)
      Several small prints have staples through the images.
    - Disney, Walt (Box A-35, Folder 29)
    - District 12 (Box A-35, Folder 30)
    - District Community School Board Five in Harlem (Box A-35, Folder 31)
    - Ditka, Mike (Box A-35, Folder 32)
    - Diton, Carl (Box A-35, Folder 33)
    - Dittmer, Richard (Box A-35, Folder 34)
    - Divas of Legacy's Rhythm and Blues Series, The (Box A-35, Folder 35)
    - Divine, Linda (Box A-35, Folder 36)
    - Dix, Sherman (Box A-35, Folder 37)
    - Dixaires, The (Box A-35, Folder 38)
    - Dixie Hummingbirds (Box A-35, Folder 39)
    - Dixieaires, The (Box A-35, Folder 40)
    - Dixon, Alexandreena D. (Box A-35, Folder 41)
    - Dixon, Arrington (Box A-35, Folder 42)
    - Dixon, Audrey (Box A-35, Folder 43)
    - Dixon, Cary (Box A-35, Folder 44)
      Black and white Polaroid print.
    - Dixon, Claude M. (Box A-35, Folder 45)
    - Dixon, Dean (Box A-35, Folder 46)
      Photographer if identified: Alix B. Williamson, Dick De Marsico
    - Dixon, Dennis (Box A-35, Folder 47)
    - Dixon, Edith (Box A-35, Folder 48)
    - Dixon, Evelyn (Box A-35, Folder 49)
    - Dixon, Florence (Box A-35, Folder 50)
    - Dixon, Testina (Box A-35, Folder 51)
    - Dixon, Glenn (Box A-35, Folder 52)
    - Dixon, Henry L. (Box A-35, Folder 53)
    - Dixon, Henry L., Jr. (Box A-35, Folder 54)
      Photographer if identified: Post Office Department
    - Dixon, Hewitt (Box A-35, Folder 55)
    - Dixon, Hortense (Dr.) (Box A-35, Folder 56)
    - Dixon, Idelle (Box A-35, Folder 57)
    - Dixon, Idelle (Box A-35, Folder 58)
    - Dixon, James O. (Box A-35, Folder 59)
    - Dixon, Ivan (Box A-35, Folder 60)
      One print shows "Dixon, Irvin", Also one velox print.
    - Dixon, Jean (Box A-35, Folder 61)
      Photographer if identified: M. Millicent MacDonald
    - Dixon, Jesse (Box A-35, Folder 62)
    - Dixon, John (Box A-35, Folder 63)
    - Dixon, Lucille (Box A-35, Folder 64)
    - Dixon, Luther (Box A-35, Folder 65)
    - Dixon, Mary (Box A-35, Folder 66)
    - Dixon, Marvin Lee (Box A-35, Folder 67)
    - Dixon, Margaret (Box A-35, Folder 68)
    - Dixon, Nathaniel (Box A-35, Folder 69)
    - Dixon, Russell (Box A-35, Folder 70)
    - Dixon, Sharon Pratt (Esq.) (Box A-35, Folder 71)
    - Dixon, Thomas, Jr. (Box A-35, Folder 72)
    - Dixon, Wayne (Box A-35, Folder 73)
      Photographer if identified: Ariel Michael
    - Dixson, Evelyn (Box A-35, Folder 74)
    - Djata, Taboo (Box A-35, Folder 75)
      Also three-leaf typescript letter "THIS IS AN OPEN LETTER TO JUDGE WHATEVER HIS NAME OF QUEENS COUNTY." Also one velox print.
    - D'Lugoff, Art (Box A-35, Folder 76)
    - D-Nice (Box A-35, Folder 77)
    - Doan, Lila, (Mrs.) (Box A-35, Folder 78)
    - Doar, John (Box A-35, Folder 79)
    - Doar, William, Jr. (Box A-35, Folder 80)
      Photographer if identified: Williams Studio West
    - Dobbins, Bruce (Box A-35, Folder 81)
    - Dobbins, Robert (Box A-35, Folder 82)
      Photographer if identified: Rumar Studios
    - Dobbs, Guy (Box A-35, Folder 83)
    - Dobbs, M. (Box A-35, Folder 84)
    - Dobler, Walter (Box A-35, Folder 85)
    - Doboso, Kodzo (Box A-35, Folder 86)
    - Dobson, Betty J. (Box A-35, Folder 87)
    - Dobson, Darlyn (Box A-35, Folder 88)
    - Dobson, Tamara (Box A-35, Folder 89)
      Also one halftone. Also one velox print.
    - Dobson, Tonsley (Box A-35, Folder 90)
    - Doby, Alvoyd (Box A-35, Folder 91)
    - Dockens, Clarence A. (Box A-35, Folder 92)
    - Dockery (Dr.) (Box A-35, Folder 93)
    - Dockery, Charles (Box A-35, Folder 94)
      Photographer if identified: Jerry Soalt
    - Dockery, George R. (and family) (Box A-35, Folder 95)
    - Dockery, George (Mrs.) (Box A-35, Folder 96)
    - Dockery Marietta (Mrs.) (Box A-35, Folder 97)
      Photographer if identified: Mike Zwerling, Harris Photo
    - Dockett, Jimmy (Box A-35, Folder 98)
      Mounted on S.I.R.M.A. advertisement with business card.
    - Doctor Glory's Children's Theater (Box A-35, Folder 99)
    - Doctor Jazz (Box A-35, Folder 100)
    - Doctors (Box A-35, Folder 101)
      Also one sheet of cardboard with 20 doctor's faces and names cut-out and mounted to the recto.
    - Dodd, John (Box A-35, Folder 102)
    - Dodd, Mother Ruth (Rev.) (Box A-35, Folder 103)
    - Dodds, Harcourt (Atty.) (Box A-35, Folder 104)
      Photographer if identified: Dick De Marsico, Willis Allen, Police Department/City of New York
    - Dodds, Malcolm (Box A-35, Folder 105)
    - Dodds, Malcolm (Box A-35, Folder 106)
    - Doddy, Reginald (Box A-35, Folder 107)
    - Dodson, Andrew (Box A-35, Folder 108)
    - Dodson, Elizabeth (Box A-35, Folder 109)
    - Dodson, Howard (Box A-35, Folder 110)
    - Dodson, James (Sgt.) (Box A-35, Folder 111)
      Also one sheet of rubylith film. Also one newspaper clipping mounted on heavy board.
    - Dodson, Marge (Box A-35, Folder 112)
    - Dodson, Samuel (Box A-35, Folder 113)
    - Dodson, Sybil (Box A-35, Folder 114)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, James Gilbert
    - Dodson, Venus (Box A-35, Folder 115)
    - Doe, Simo (Box A-35, Folder 116)
    - Dogan, Sara L. (Box A-35, Folder 117)
    - Dodge, Harcourt (Box A-35, Folder 118)
    - Doggy Dogg, Snoop (Box A-35, Folder 119)
    - Doggett, Bill (Box A-35, Folder 120)
      Also two paper stereotype matrices.
    - Dolan, Henry (Box A-35, Folder 121)
    - Doles, Roxie (Box A-35, Folder 122)
    - Dollar Brand (Box A-35, Folder 123)
    - Doll League (Box A-35, Folder 124)
      About seven prints are stuck together in a group. About three prints are stuck to the folder.
    - Dolls (Box A-35, Folder 125)
    - Dolly, Cyril (Dr.) (Box A-35, Folder 126)
    - Dollymore, Victor (Box A-35, Folder 127)
    - Dolphy, Eric (Box A-35, Folder 128)
    - Dolphyns, The (Box A-35, Folder 129)
    - Domains (Box A-35, Folder 130)
    - Doman, Elvira Hand (Box A-35, Folder 131)
    - Domestic Peace Corps (Associated Community Teams) (Box A-35, Folder 132)
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews, Oscar Mallory, Donald J. Charles
    - Domingo, Wilfred A. (Box A-35, Folder 133)
      Photographer if identified: Wally Allen
    - Dominican Republic (Box A-35, Folder 134)
    - Domino, Fats (Box A-35, Folder 135)
    - Domino One Ltd., President Geraldine Young (Box A-35, Folder 136)
    - Dominoes, The (Box A-35, Folder 137)
    - Donahue, Oscar (Box A-35, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: March of Dimes
    - Donoghue, Roger (Box A-35, Folder 139)
    - Donald, Marlene (Box A-35, Folder 140)
    - Donadio, Carl S. (Box A-35, Folder 141)
    - Donahue, Jerry (Box A-35, Folder 142)
    - Donaldson, Andrew G. (Box A-35, Folder 143)
      Also two velox prints. About five prints have badly darkened and discolored.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, B&G International Photos, Jesse Wegweiser, Chester Color Studios, Ralph Cooper
    - Donaldson, Bobby (Box A-35, Folder 144)
      Including one photographic post card.
    - Donaldson, Boston (Box A-35, Folder 145)
    - Donaldson, Enoch (Box A-35, Folder 146)
    - Donaldson, Lou (Box A-35, Folder 147)
    - Donaldson, Morse (Box A-35, Folder 148)
    - Donaldson, Norma (Box A-35, Folder 149)
    - Donaldson, William H. (Box A-35, Folder 150)
    - Donawa, Robert R. (Box A-35, Folder 151)
    - Donegan, Charles (Box A-35, Folder 152)
    - Donegan, Dorothy (Box A-35, Folder 153)
      Includes one (possibly misfiled) print of "Charles Donegan."
      Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, James Gilbert
    - Donegan, Elizabeth (Box A-35, Folder 154)
    - Donegan, Horace W.B. (Rt. Rev.) (Box A-35, Folder 155)
      Newspaper clipping adhered to the verso of one print.
    - Donesa, Carmen (Box A-35, Folder 156)
    - Donizulu, Gus (Box A-35, Folder 157)
    - Donnell, Prince and Donnell Dancers (Box A-35, Folder 158)
    - Donnell, Horace (Box A-35, Folder 159)
      Photographer if identified: Dagmar
    - Donnson, Jonathan (Box A-35, Folder 160)
    - Donovan, Bernard E. (Box A-35, Folder 161)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Bro. David McAdams, Board of Education/City of New York
    - Donovan, James B. (Box A-35, Folder 162)
      Photographer if identified: The New York Times, Board of Education/City of New York, Bro. David McAdams, Fabian Bachrach
    - Donovan, Joan (Box A-35, Folder 163)
    - Donovan, Selby (Mr.) (Box A-35, Folder 164)
    - Donzell, Modeen (Box A-35, Folder 165)
    - Don Q (Rum) (Box A-35, Folder 166)
    - Doobie Social Club (Box A-35, Folder 167)
    - Doodletown Pipers, The (Box A-35, Folder 168)
    - Doods, Reginald (Box A-35, Folder 169)
    - Dooley, James "Stoney" (Box A-35, Folder 170)
    - Dooley, Jimmy (Box A-35, Folder 171)
    - Dopson, Betty J. (Box A-35, Folder 172)
    - Dopson, Betty J. (Box A-35, Folder 173)
    - Dor, David (Box A-35, Folder 174)
    - Dora, Olu (Box A-35, Folder 175)
    - Doran, Laura (Box A-35, Folder 176)
    - Dore, David (Box A-35, Folder 177)
    - Dore, Lanell (Box A-35, Folder 178)
    - Dorham, Kenny (Box A-35, Folder 179)
    - Dorman, Frank S. (Box A-35, Folder 180)
      Laminated passport photo. Also one velox print.
    - Dorman's "Kids Who Can Cook" Contest (Box A-35, Folder 181)
    - Dorn, James (Box A-35, Folder 182)
    - Dorn, Michael (Box A-35, Folder 183)
    - D'ors, The (Box A-35, Folder 184)
    - Dorrian, Joe (Box A-35, Folder 185)
    - Dorsett, Anthony and Tony (Box A-35, Folder 186)
    - Dorsett, Thomas A. (Box A-35, Folder 187)
    - Dorsett, Tony (Box A-35, Folder 188)
    - Dorsey, Beverly Louise (Box A-35, Folder 189)
    - Dorsey, Edmund (Box A-35, Folder 190)
    - Dorsey, Edward C. (Box A-35, Folder 191)
    - Dorsey, Esther (Box A-35, Folder 192)
    - Dorsey, Lula (Box A-35, Folder 193)
    - Dorsey, Ralph (Box A-35, Folder 194)
    - Dorsey, Ronald (Box A-35, Folder 195)
    - Dorsey, Thomas (Dr.) (Box A-35, Folder 196)
    - Doss, Earther (Box A-35, Folder 197)
    - Doswell, Morris (Box A-35, Folder 198)
      Includes five (possibly misfiled) prints of "Marjorie Doswell" and photos from her memorial service. Also includes the program from her memorial service.
    - Dotson, Betty Low (Box A-35, Folder 199)
    - Dotson, Heyward (Box A-35, Folder 200)
    - Dotson, Howard (Box A-35, Folder 201)
    - Dotson, John (Box A-35, Folder 202)
    - Dotton, Frank (Box A-35, Folder 203)
    - Dotts, Dorothy (Box A-35, Folder 204)